Syam Yadavalli

Guntur, Andhra Pradesh, India

syamkumaryadavalli@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/syam-yadavalli-9701551a7

Summary

I am a tech enthusiast interested in Web & App development and Data Science. Experienced Event Management specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the industry. skilled in Python, C+, JavaScript, React, Django, Data Analytics and Photo & video editing skills. Passionate Developer with Bachelor of Technology (B. Tech) focused in Biotech Engineering from National Institute of Technology, Raipur.

Experience



dominattor

Mar 2022 - Present (2 months +)

Core Coordinator

AAVARTAN, NIT Raipur

Dec 2021 - Present (5 months +)

Core Mentor

Sahyog - The mentorship club, NIT RAIPUR Jun 2021 - Jan 2022 (8 months)

Executive

AAVARTAN, NIT Raipur

Nov 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Frontend Developer

NxtGen Esports

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 (3 months)

Education



National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Biotechnology 2019 - 2023

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Data Analysis • Web Development • Front-end Development • Biotechnology • Django • C++ • React.js • JavaScript • Bootstrap